fullscreen.com 2017-11-30

# Privacy Policy

## Summary

_Welcome to Fullscreen! We collect personal information you choose to share with us and our partners so we can better provide a customized entertainment offering for you, and to manage your account. Your information is kept secure through industry norms, but security can be breached, especially if you are not careful with protecting your username and password. You can modify your information through your account settings, but we may retain your information on an aggregate, non personally-identifiable basis for bona fide business purposes even if you are no longer a registered user or customer._

## 1\. Introduction to Fullscreen and this Privacy Policy

We at Fullscreen, Inc. ("Company," "We," "Us," "Our") know that our users ("you," "your") care about how your personally identifiable information ("Information") is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy (the "Policy") as it relates to your use of any of the services, sites, applications, offerings, or products that we offer (collectively, the "Service"). By visiting or using the Service in any manner, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Policy and our Terms of Service. 

We do not knowingly collect or solicit Information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register for the Service. 

## 2\. What Information We Collect

#### Information You Provide to Us

When you sign up for the Service, we collect a variety of information from you that you provide, including registration information such as your name, birth date or age range, gender, email address and physical address, and, if you are paying for the Service, payment information (credit or debit card number, CVC and billing zip code). If you choose to log-in through third-party account credentials (for example, your Facebook login), some of your Information may be shared with us or the respective third-party platform, as disclosed to you at the time of log-in. 

#### Information Collected Automatically By Us

Whenever you interact with our Service, we automatically receive and record technical information such as your device, IP address, "cookie" information (as described in our Cookie Policy, the version of your operating system ("OS"), and the page you requested. When you use the Service on a mobile platform, we may also collect and record your unique device ID (persistent / non-persistent), hardware type, media access control ("MAC") address, international mobile equipment identity ("IMEI"), your device name, and your location (based on your IP address). We may also collect information regarding your activity on the Service (both individually and on an aggregate basis) and your interactions with other users of the Service. 

#### Information from Third Parties

We work with third party service providers who assist us in managing or providing the Service (e.g., payment processors) and who collect some of the information described above. We may also collect contextual or demographic data about our users from third parties, in order to more effectively deliver the Service or content in which we think you would be interested. Unless you have been notified otherwise, all information collected through our authorized third party service providers remains governed by security and confidentiality obligations consistent with this Policy and applicable law. 

#### Third Party Advertisements

We may feature third party advertising within the Service and/or on a third party website or application created using the Service ("User Site"). Such advertisers may collect and use Information about you in order to provide advertisements of interest to you. This Privacy Policy shall apply with respect to advertising appearing within the Service, and the User Site's privacy policy shall apply with respect to advertising appearing on the applicable User Site. 

## Cookies and Similar Technologies

Read our Cookie Policy to learn more about how we use cookies and similar technologies. 

## 3\. Why We Collect Information

The primary reason we collect Information is to manage your account and subscription to our Service, and to provide more customized Service to our audience, including content, programming, or other entertainment experiences that we think you will enjoy. 

Other important reasons we collect Information are as follows: 

  1. To communicate with you regarding the Service, content offerings, and for marketing and promotional purposes (we may contact you by means of any of the Information you provide to us, subject to your consent where required by law);
  2. To ensure technical functionality and delivery of the Service; and
  3. To provide ad-supported content offerings which are provided by marketers interested in reaching our general demographic audience.

## 4\. How Your Information is Shared

### 4.1 Sharing by you

The Service is social by its very nature, so your participation in the Service will allow others to see your name and/or username, profile picture, and social profile. 

Certain user-profile information, including without limitation a user's name, location, and any video or image content that such user has uploaded to the Service, may be displayed to other users to facilitate user interaction within the Service or address your request for Company's services. Your account privacy settings allow you to limit the other users who can see the Personal Information in your user profile and/or what information in your user profile is visible to others. Any content you upload to your public user profile, along with any Personal Information or content that you voluntarily disclose online in a manner other users can view (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, etc.) becomes publicly available, and can be collected and used by others. Your user name may also be displayed to other users if and when you send messages or comments or upload images or videos through the Service and other users can contact you through messages and comments. Additionally, if you sign into the Service through a third party social networking site or service, your list of "friends" from that site or service may be automatically imported to the Service, and such "friends," if they are also registered users of the Service, may be able to access certain non-public information you have entered in your Service user-profile. Again, we do not control the policies and practices of any other third party site or service. 

Some parts of our Service will enable you to share your interactions with our Service, such as content viewed, user generated content posted, and other social interactions. If you connect to our Service through a third party application (e.g., Facebook), then you further understand that we may automatically share your interactions with our Service with that third party application. 

### 4.2 Sharing by us

We share your Information with third parties as listed below and as otherwise described elsewhere in this Policy: 

#### Service Providers

We employ third parties to perform tasks on our behalf, such as payment processing, data management and analytics, marketing, communication and IT services, and we need to share your Information with them in order for them to provide such products and services. Unless we tell you differently or you consent otherwise, these third parties do not have any right to use your Information beyond what is necessary to assist us in providing such products and services. Any uses of your Information by these third parties will remain governed by security and confidentiality obligations consistent with this Policy and applicable law. 

#### Fullscreen Affiliates

Subject to applicable laws, we may share your Information with companies with whom Fullscreen is affiliated or related to (e.g., parent company or subsidiaries), and will require such affiliated or related companies to use the Information solely in accordance with this Policy. 

#### Business Transfers

We may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer Information is typically one of the business assets that would be transferred. Also, if we (or our assets) are acquired or merged, or if we go out of business, enter bankruptcy, or go through some other change of control, Information would be one of the assets transferred to or acquired by a third party. 

#### Protection of Company and Others

We reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any Information that we reasonably believe is necessary to comply with law or court order; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, interests, or safety of our Company, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

#### With Your Consent

Subject to your consent, we may share your Information with third party businesses or sites that we do not control. In those instances, your Information will be subject to their separate privacy policies and you should review those policies in advance before providing consent. 

#### User Sites

We may share your Information collected using the Service on the User Site with the creators and/or administrators of such User Site. Such User Site will be subject to a separate privacy policy governing the User Site's collection and use of your information, so please carefully review such separate privacy policy before using the User Site. To the extent that there is a conflict between the provisions of this Privacy Policy and the provisions of the User Site's privacy policy, if any, then the provisions of this Privacy Policy shall apply with respect to our use of Information and the User Site's privacy policy shall apply with respect to the User Site's use of Information. 

## 5\. The Security of Your Information

Your account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You must prevent unauthorized access to your account and Information by selecting and protecting your password and/or other sign-on mechanism appropriately. To help protect your Information, you should not share your account information or password, reuse your password on other sites, or use a password you have used on other sites. 

We endeavor to protect the privacy of your account and other Information we hold in our records, but we cannot guarantee complete security. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time. 

## 6\. Where Your Information Will Be Held

In order to provide the Service, the Information that we collect from you may be transferred to and stored at a destination outside of your country and the European Economic Area ("EEA"), and, in particular, the United States. It may also be processed by any service providers appointed by us who operate outside of the EEA and their staff. By submitting your data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing outside of the EEA or your country and acknowledge that not all countries guarantee the same level of protection for your Information as the one in which you reside. Data transferred will be treated in accordance with this Policy. 

## 7\. What Information You Can Access

Through your account settings for the Service, you may access, edit, or delete Information you've provided and your record of interactions with the Service. Such Information and interactions, and your ability to update them, will vary based on the Service. 

## 8\. What Choices You Have

You can always opt not to disclose Information or to disable certain tools on your browser or device. However, this may limit your ability to fully utilize the Service. 

You may be able to add, update, or delete Information as explained in the "What Information You Can Access" section above. When you update Information, however, we may maintain a copy of the unrevised Information in our records. Please note that some Information may remain in our records for legitimate business reasons even after your deletion of such Information, such as our analyzing aggregated data regarding past usage of the Service (but not in a manner that would identify you personally). 

You can opt in to receive mobile push notifications from Fullscreen. If you change your mind later and no longer want to receive these notifications, you can use your device's settings functionality to turn them off. 

If you don't want to receive e-mail or other communications from us, you can adjust your email preferences from your account, or opt-out by clicking on the link provided in the emails. 

To learn more about choices regarding cookies set through the Service, see our Cookie Policy. 

## 9\. Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may amend this Policy from time to time. Use of Information we collect now is subject to the Policy in effect at the time such Information is used. If we make material changes to this Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement through the applicable Service or by otherwise notifying you through contact means you have provided prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to regularly review this page any updates to our Policy. You are bound by any changes to the Policy when you use any of our Service after such changes have been first posted. 

## 10\. Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our Policy, please send us a detailed message at the address below, and we will try to resolve your concerns. 

Fullscreen, Inc.  
12180 Millennium Dr.  
Los Angeles, CA 90094  
help@fullscreen.com  
Attn: Privacy 

## 10\. Your California Privacy Rights

Under California Civil Code Sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice identifying the categories of personal Information that we share with our affiliates and/or third parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such affiliates and/or third parties. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: Fullscreen, Inc., 12180 Millennium Dr., Los Angeles, CA 90094. We will respond to one request per California customer each year, and we do not respond to requests made by means other than as set forth above. 

California Do Not Track Disclosure: Do Not Track is a privacy preference that users can set in their web browsers. When a user turns on the Do Not Track signal, the browser sends a message to websites requesting them not to track the user. At this time, we do not respond to Web browser "do not track" settings or signals. As described in our Cookies section, we deploy cookies and other technologies on our Service to collect information about you and your browsing activity, even if you have turned on the Do Not Track signal. 

_Last Updated: April 26, 2016_

_To see the prior version of this Privacy Policy, go to<https://fullscreenmedia.co/legal/#privacy-policy>._
